Guide to the C. Harrison Mann, Jr. Map Collection, 1579-1961
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- C. Harrison Mann, Jr. Map Collection
  - Lyon Park, 1,000 Lots and Acreage (of Clarendon, Virginia), June 1, 1920 (Folder 94)
  - Map of Alexandria County, Virginia Formerly Part of the District of Columbia, July 1907 (Folder 95)